<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LifeTune</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!-- Auth UI -->
    <string name="launch_title">FirebaseUI Auth Demo</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>

    <string name="unknown_response">Unexpected onActivityResult response code</string>
    <string name="unknown_sign_in_response">Unknown response from AuthUI sign-in</string>
    <string name="sign_in_cancelled">Sign in cancelled</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">No internet connection</string>
    <string name="unknown_error">An unknown error occurred</string>
    <string name="search_music_title">Search music</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_waiting_message">Waiting for a minute</string>
    <string name="api_service_error_title">Sorry! I\'m Wrong</string>
    <string name="api_service_error_message">There are some problems occurred while accessing to our service. We are fixing as fast as possible. Please contact me at beantoan@gmail.com for more helps.</string>
    <string name="no_internet_error_title">No internet connection</string>
    <string name="no_internet_error_message">Please check your wifi or mobile data connection</string>
    <string name="dummy_text">
        Much like Bitcoin, the blockchain can be used to find the state of the system at any point in time. This can be done by replaying each transaction from the very first block up to the point in question. However, in contrast to Bitcoin, most nodes do not keep a full copy of the data for every point in time. Ethereum allows for old data to be pruned from the blockchain. The blockchain remains consistent as long as the blocks are valid, and data is stored outside of the blocks, so technically it is not required to verify the proof-of-work chain. In contrast to Bitcoin, where to find the balance of an account a node must replay all transactions leading up to that point, Ethereum stores state by keeping the root hash of the Merkle Patricia Tree in each block. As long as the data for the last block (or any past blocks) is available, future operations can be performed in the Ethereum network. In other words, it is not necessary for the network to replay old transactions, since their result is already available. This would be akin to storing the balance of each account in each block in the Bitcoin network.
        For our purposes, the Merkle aspect of the trees are what matter in Ethereum. Rather than keeping the whole tree inside a block, the hash of its root node is embedded in the block. If some malicious node were to tamper with the state of the blockchain, it would become evident as soon as other nodes computed the hash of the root node using the tampered data. The resulting hash would simply not match with the one recorded in the block. At this point we should find ourselves asking a big question: why not simply take the hash of the data? Merkle Patricia Trees are used in Ethereum for a different, but very important reason: most of the time, nodes do not need a full copy of the whole state of the system. Rather, they want to have a partial view of the state, complete enough to perform any necessary computations for newer blocks or to read the state from some specific address. Since no computations usually require access to the whole state stored in the blockchain, downloading all state would be superfluous. In fact, if nodes had to do this, scalability would be a serious concern as the network expanded. To verify a partial piece of the state at a given point, a node need only download the data necessary for a branch of the tree and the hashes of its siblings. Any change in the data stored at a leaf would require a malicious node to be able to carry a preimage attack against the hashing algorithm of the tree (to find the values for the siblings that combined with the modified data produce the same root hash as the one stored in the block).
        
        Bean Bean Bean
    </string>
    <string name="no_song_play">There is no song</string>
    <string name="song_is_be_loading">Song is being loaded ...</string>
    <string name="request_access_fine_location">Please accept location permission to use the features</string>
    <string name="request_access_fine_location_error_title">Provide location permission</string>
    <string name="request_access_fine_location_error_message">Please turn on location permission in app setting to use the features</string>
    <string name="error_turn_on_location_title">Cannot turn on location</string>
    <string name="error_turn_on_location_message">Please turn on location to receive the best recommendation</string>
    <string name="count_steps_chart_title">Count Steps</string>
    <string name="calculate_distances_chart_title">Calculate Distances</string>
    <string name="calculate_calories_chart_title">Calculate Calories</string>
    <string name="my_activities_summary_title">Summary</string>
    <string name="fitness_read_history_error_title">Sorry! I\'m Wrong</string>
    <string name="fitness_read_history_error_message">There are some problems occurred while retrieving fitness data. We are fixing as fast as possible. Please contact me at beantoan@gmail.com for more helps.</string>
    <string name="get_nearby_places_error_title">Sorry! I\'m Wrong</string>
    <string name="get_nearby_places_error_message">There are some problems occurred while retrieving nearby places. We are fixing as fast as possible. Please contact me at beantoan@gmail.com for more helps.</string>
    <string name="summary_active_time_title">Active time</string>
    <string name="summary_steps_title">Steps</string>
    <string name="summary_distance_title">Distance</string>
    <string name="summary_calories_title">Calories</string>
    <string name="nav_play_music_title">Play music</string>
    <string name="nav_my_activities_title">My Activities</string>
    <string name="nav_schedules_title">Schedules</string>
    <string name="nav_nearby_places_title">Nearby Places</string>
    <string name="nav_settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="nav_my_profile_title">My Profile</string>
    <string name="nav_logout_title">Logout</string>
    <string name="button_show_map_title">Show map</string>
    <string name="get_current_location_error_message">Cannot locate your location</string>
    <string name="button_hide_map_title">Hide map</string>
    <string name="locating_location_title">Locating your location ...</string>

</resources>
